The Kingdom of Myrtana, united by King Rhobar II.
During the long years of his reign, Rhobar was able to defeat all foes of his realm. All except one.
The war against the orcs took its toll, and the enemy acted quickly and ruthlessly.
The war was going on month after month, and the economy of the kingdom was plunging into an inevitable crisis.
The solution to this problem was to increase the number of miners on the island of Khorinis.
Criminals were sentenced to work in the penal colony also known as the Valley of Mines.
Meanwhile, to break the impasse on the front, the king sent the whole might of his fleet,
attempting to prevent the enemy’s conquest of strategically important islands of the Eastern Archipelago.
But the admirals misjudged the situation. The orcs turned out to be equally skilled warriors on land and water.
The fleet of Myrtana, in just a few hours, fell to the bottom of the sea,
and the nearby island Archolos, the capital of the archipelago, was to pay the price.
Determined to maintain control over the region, the king ordered to seize every ship, including vessels of Araxos Guild,
and use them to carry soldiers to war.
Every able-bodied citizen, no matter how rich or poor, was soon to be conscripted into the king’s army.
The decree, however, only fueled the fire already burning in people’s hearts.
Inner conflicts resulting from the vast diversity of its residents made Archolos boil
and with every new wave of refugees coming to its shores, the pot was closer and closer to spill.
On the remote island of Londram, two brothers are preparing to leave for Archolos, hoping to escape the clutches of war.